Ralph Waldo Emerson once said that the purpose of life is not to be happy, but to be useful, to be loving, to make some difference in the world.
拉尔夫·沃尔多·爱默生曾说，人生的目的不是快乐，而是做个有用的人，心怀爱意，给世界带来一些改变。
While we appreciate such words of wisdom, we rarely try to follow them in our lives.
虽然我们欣赏这样的至理名言，却很少在生活中努力践行。
Most people prefer to live a good life themselves, ignoring their responsibilities for the world.
大多数人更愿意自己过上美好生活，而忽视自己对世界应负的责任。
This narrow perception of a good life may provide short-term benefits, but is sure to lead to long-term harm and suffering.
这种对美好生活的狭隘认识或许能带来短期的好处，但必定会导致长期的危害和痛苦。
A good life based on comfort and luxury may eventually lead to more pain because we spoil our health and even our character, principles, ideals, and relationships.
建立在舒适和奢华之上的美好生活最终可能带来更多痛苦，因为我们会毁掉自己的健康，甚至毁掉自己的品格、原则、理想和人际关系。
What, then, is the secret of a good life?
那么，美好生活的秘诀是什么呢？
A good life is a process, not a state of being: a direction, not a destination.
美好生活是一个过程，而不是一种固定不变的状态；是一个方向，而不是一个终点。
We have to earn a good life by first serving others without any expectation in return because their happiness is the very source of our own happiness.
我们必须先为他人服务、不求任何回报，以此赢得美好生活，因为他人的幸福恰恰是我们自身幸福的源泉。
More importantly, we must know ourselves inside out.
更重要的是，我们必须彻底了解自己。
Only when we examine ourselves deeply can we discover our abilities and recognize our limitations, and then work accordingly to create a better world.
只有深入审视自己，我们才能发现自身的能力，认清自身的局限，进而据此努力，创造一个更美好的世界。
The first requirement for a good life is having a loving heart.
美好生活的首要条件是拥有一颗充满爱的心。
When we do certain right things merely as a duty, we find our job so tiresome that we’ll soon burn out.
如果我们只是把某些正确的事当作义务去做，就会觉得这件事太累人，很快就会精疲力竭。
However, when we do that same job out of love, we not only enjoy what we do, but also do it with an effortless feeling.
然而，如果我们出于爱去做同一件事，就不仅会享受所做的事，而且做起来毫不费力。
However, love alone is insufficient to lead a good life.
然而，仅有爱并不足以过上美好生活。
Love sometimes blinds us to the reality.
爱有时会让我们看不清现实。
Consequently, our good intentions may not lead to good results.
因此，我们的良好意愿未必能带来好的结果。
To achieve the desired outcome, those who want to do good to others also need to equip themselves with accurate world knowledge.
为了达到预期的结果，想要善待他人的人还需要用关于世界的准确知识来武装自己。
False knowledge is more dangerous than ignorance.
错误的知识比无知更危险。
If love is the engine of a car, knowledge is the steering wheel.
如果说爱是汽车的发动机，那么知识就是方向盘。
If the engine lacks power, the car can’t move; if the driver loses control of the steering, a road accident will probably occur.
如果发动机动力不足，汽车就无法行驶；如果司机控制不住方向，很可能就会发生交通事故。
Only with love in our hearts and the right knowledge in mind can we lead a good life.
只有心中有爱、头脑中有正确的知识，我们才能过上美好生活。
With love and knowledge, we go all out to create a better world by doing good to others.
有了爱和知识，我们就会全力以赴，通过善待他人来创造一个更美好的世界。
When we see the impact of our good work on the world, we give meaning to our life and earn lasting joy and happiness.
看到自己的善举给世界带来的影响，我们便赋予了人生意义，并收获持久的快乐与幸福。